Juan Ignacio Maraude

Full Stack Web Developer

Juan Ignacio Maraude

Mar del Plata, Buenos Aires Province, Argentina

maraudenacho@gmail.com

LinkedIn

GitHub

Cellphone: +54 9 2235354526

I am curious and decisive, I enjoy detecting and fixing mistakes, and I am a practical person who is constantly using his knowledge to solve real problems.

I have experience in agile methodologies such as Scrum and skills in handling new tools such as Redux Toolkit and Tailwind, skills that I acquired in my training process during the boot camp at Henry and while developing my final project. I am very interested in continuing to work as a Full Stack Developer and contributing to the development of organizations from the tech world.

Skills

Node.js, Express, Sequelize, Scrum, Tailwind

HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Redux, Redux Toolkit, PostgreSQL,

Experience

Full Stack Web Developer - Video games App

Henry Bootcamp

(June 2022 - July 2022)

- Design and development of a video game App that included: searching, filtering, sorting, and creation.
- Develop the app using React, Redux, and native CSS at the FrontEnd, and Node.js with Express at the BackEnd. Database in PostgreSQL and Sequelize.

Video Games App

Front End Web Developer - Foodify App

Henry Bootcamp

(July 2022 - August 2022)

- Design and develop combined filters, searches, and sorting in all the necessary components.
- Integrate Redux Toolkit into the application and instruct the other members of the project on its use.
- Finding and adjusting defects in the operation of the application (Debugging).

Foodify App

Education

- Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 700 hours of theoretical-practical course. 2022
- Programming at the University of Technology (March 2021 -July 2021)

Languages

- Spanish: Native
- English: Upper Intermediate (B2) <u>EFSET Certificate</u>